<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Nationwide IT]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nationwide IT]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/news</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 16:44:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nw-its.com/blog-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[NIS wins IT Operations Center monitoring (ITOC) (January 2023)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce the award of a new three year contract providing IT Operations Center monitoring...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-wins-it-operations-center-monitoring-itoc-january-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63cf06088d074a44187a7ca2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 22:11:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_c184a132612849f4ba9de71338fadf79~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>sonnguyen60</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce the award of a new three year contract providing IT Operations Center monitoring (ITOC) for the Defense Logistics Agency (DLA) Information Operations (J6) office under our J6 Enterprise Technology Services (JETS) contract vehicle. NIS won this competitive award through the Group C pool.  For the DLA's IT Operations Center monitoring, NIS is responsible for providing twenty-four by seven (24x7) support on critical applications and network devices three hundred sixty-five (365) days a year for its user population as well as those of DoD, DLA, and Contractor entities and the activities that these organizations support on DLA operated facilities.  </p>

<p>DLA JETS provides the full range of IT services, technical and management expertise that support applications, software, hardware, infrastructure, and systems, across the DLA IT Enterprise. Support includes information technology solutions, technical support, maintenance, and sustainment; operations support; application development, maintenance and technical support; and lifecycle management.  NIS is a contract holder in Group C 8(a) which currently only has three (3) companies.  </p>

<p>NIS is pleased to provide DLA with critical support services that enable DLA to fulfil its mission of supporting the Warfighter first. For more information on how NIS can assist you, please contact <a href="mailto:BD@nw-its.com"  >BD@nw-its.com</a><<a href="mailto:BD@nw-its.com"  >mailto:BD@nw-its.com</a>> or call 703-750-0453.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_c184a132612849f4ba9de71338fadf79~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS wins Enterprise Infrastructure Installation Support (EIIS) (January 2023)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce the award of a new three year contract providing Enterprise Infrastructure...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-wins-enterprise-infrastructure-installation-support-eiis-january-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63cf05267cc83c394f25badc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 22:10:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_c184a132612849f4ba9de71338fadf79~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>sonnguyen60</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce the award of a new three year contract providing Enterprise Infrastructure Installation Support (EIIS) for the Defense Logistics Agency (DLA) Information Operations (J6) office under our J6 Enterprise Technology Services (JETS) contract vehicle. NIS won this competitive award through the Group C pool.  For the DLA's Enterprise Infrastructure Installation Support services, NIS is responsible for providing engineering services to furnish, install, secure, and test the DLA's IT infrastructure and Information Systems to support and sustain the infrastructure and networking equipment worldwide. </p>

<p>DLA JETS provides the full range of IT services, technical and management expertise that support applications, software, hardware, infrastructure, and systems, across the DLA IT Enterprise. Support includes information technology solutions, technical support, maintenance, and sustainment; operations support; application development, maintenance and technical support; and lifecycle management.  NIS is a contract holder in Group C 8(a) which currently only has three (3) companies.  </p>

<p>NIS is pleased to provide DLA with critical support services that enable DLA to fulfil its mission of supporting the Warfighter first. For more information on how NIS can assist you, please contact <a href="mailto:BD@nw-its.com"  >BD@nw-its.com</a><<a href="mailto:BD@nw-its.com"  >mailto:BD@nw-its.com</a>> or call 703-750-0453.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_c184a132612849f4ba9de71338fadf79~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS wins DLA NIPR/SIPR Access Management (December 2022)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce the award of a new three year contract providing NIPR/SIPR Access Management and...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-wins-dla-nipr-sipr-access-management-december-2022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63cf035256a66ea887b94b25</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 22:06:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_c184a132612849f4ba9de71338fadf79~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>sonnguyen60</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce the award of a new three year contract providing NIPR/SIPR Access Management and Trusted Agent Support for the Defense Logistics Agency (DLA) Information Operations (J6) office under our J6 Enterprise Technology Services (JETS) contract vehicle. NIS won this competitive award through the Group C pool.  For DLA's NIPR/SIPR Access Management and Trusted Agent Support services, NIS supports the DLA Access Control program by ensuring confidentiality, integrity, and non-repudiation of sensitive and classified information systems. NIS is responsible for supporting access and provisioning accounts to DOD and DLA computer systems and applications.  </p>

<p>DLA JETS provides the full range of IT services, technical and management expertise that support applications, software, hardware, infrastructure, and systems, across the DLA IT Enterprise. Support includes information technology solutions, technical support, maintenance, and sustainment; operations support; application development, maintenance and technical support; and lifecycle management.  NIS is a contract holder in Group C 8(a) which currently only has three (3) companies. </p>

<p>NIS is pleased to provide DLA with critical support services that enable DLA to fulfil its mission of supporting the Warfighter first. For more information on how NIS can assist you, please contact <a href="mailto:BD@nw-its.com" target="_blank" >BD@nw-its.com</a><<a href="mailto:BD@nw-its.com" target="_blank" >mailto:BD@nw-its.com</a>> or call 703-750-0453</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_c184a132612849f4ba9de71338fadf79~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS Receives 2022 HIRE Vets Medallion Award from the U.S. Department of Labor (November 2022)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nationwide IT Services, Inc. (NIS) is pleased to announce that we have been awarded the Platinum award in the Honoring Investments in...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-receives-2022-hire-vets-medallion-award-from-the-u-s-department-of-labor-november-2022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">636d179246c1017adf26db9f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 15:43:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/bc49a4_96ea4c370657407bb435ee383bf8258c~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_542,h_538,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>sonnguyen60</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nationwide IT Services, Inc. (NIS) is pleased to announce that we have been awarded the Platinum award in the Honoring Investments in Recruiting and Employing American Military Veterans Act (HIRE Vets Act) Medallion Program for the second year in a row. </p>

<p>This year, the U.S. Department of Labor selected 835 employers for the 2022 HIRE Vets Medallion award and the award event was conducted via a virtual ceremony. NIS' President and CEO, CK Park was asked to be one of three (3) companies to represent the 835 awardees in person at the U.S. Department of Labor Headquarters in Washington D.C for the November 9, 2022 awards ceremony. The Department of Labor Secretary, Martin J. Walsh recognized NIS and the other awardees at this ceremony and asked the three CEO's specific questions about their experience with the Medallion program. The ceremony can be viewed here: <a href="https://www.hirevets.gov/ceremony" target="_blank" >www.HIREVets.gov/ceremony</a>. </p>

<p>The HIRE Vets Act Medallion Program is the only federal award program that recognizes employers who successfully recruit, hire, and retain veterans. CK Park stated during the ceremony on November 9, 2022, "As an Army veteran, I truly value the HIRE Vets program and especially recognize the priority that is being placed on hiring Vets. Hiring veterans is critical. Our company culture is built around military service and everything we do is built around servicing our nation and our taxpayers. We found that veterans and military training builds directly into our culture of adding value with integrity. We are honored and appreciate being part of the HIRE Vets program." </p>

<p>NIS joins 835 other companies from 49 states, plus the District of Columbia, who have shown a commitment to hiring veterans, but also ensuring that they have a long-term career and growth plan that uses the diverse skills they acquired through their military service. Recipients of the 2022 HIRE Vets Medallion Award meet rigorous employment and veteran integration assistance criteria, including veteran hiring and retention percentages; availability of veteran-specific resources; leadership programming for veterans; dedicated human resource efforts; pay compensation and tuition assistance programs for veterans. About Nationwide IT Services NIS is an IT and Management consulting company, designated 8(a) by the SBA, and a CVE-verified Service Disabled Veteran Owned Small Business. Our mission is to deliver value-added services to our customers, leveraging technology, people, and industry best practices to implement innovative solutions through our trusted employees and team members. NIS is always looking for Veterans to join the team and anyone interested learning more about it should visit <a href="https://www.nw-its.com/veterans" target="_blank" ><u>www.nw-its.com/veterans</u></a>. </p>

<p>About the HIRE Vets Medallion Program </p>

<p>The HIRE Vets Medallion Award is earned by businesses that demonstrate unparalleled commitment to attracting, hiring, and retaining veterans. The 2023 HIRE Vets Medallion Award application period will open to employers on Jan. 31, 2023. For more information about the program and the application process, visit <a href="https://hirevets.gov/" target="_blank" >HIREVets.gov</a>. There are different awards for large employers (500-plus employees), medium employers (51-499 employees), and small employers (50 or fewer employees). Additionally, there are two award tiers: platinum and gold.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/bc49a4_96ea4c370657407bb435ee383bf8258c~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_542,h_538,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS has been selected as Finalist in the GovCon Awards(tm) (Sep 30, 2022)]]></title><description><![CDATA[NIS is honored to announce that we have been selected as a finalist in the Contractor of the Year: $25 - $75 Million category for the...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-has-been-selected-as-finalist-in-the-govcon-awards-tm-sep-30-2022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63374f32e76d3e690b4c11cf</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:23:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_28c2ab78203046e5b35941d70e416648~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_200,h_200,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NIS is honored to announce that we have been selected as a finalist in the Contractor of the Year: $25 - $75 Million category for the 20th Annual Greater Washington Government Contractor Awards(tm).  These awards honor innovative companies, industry heavyweights and long-time pillars in the government contracting community for their commitment to excellence and role in shaping the marketplace.  We Thank our entire staff for their hard work, dedication, and commitment to building one of the best Government Contracting businesses in the DC Area!  We also thank the Northern Virginia Chamber of Commerce and look forward to November 2, 2022, when the winner is announced.  WE Are Nationwide IT Services!</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_28c2ab78203046e5b35941d70e416648~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_200,h_200,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS wins BPA supporting the U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) Water Mission Area (WMA) (June 2022) ]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is excited to announce a new (5) year contract award from the USGS Water Mission Area (WMA) Blanket Purchase...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-wins-bpa-supporting-the-u-s-geological-survey-usgs-water-mission-area-wma-june-2022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62d1b719ec14ca6070712dc1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 18:51:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_e357c64f59a540c58b7a8dda5a8bbd84~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_740,h_495,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is excited to announce a new (5) year contract award from the USGS Water Mission Area (WMA) Blanket Purchase Agreement (BPA) for IT Services. C.K. Park, CEO of NIS, said: "We are grateful for the opportunity to support the WMA on its science mission and continue supporting USGS with our industry leading solutions and innovations. This is also an important indicator that NIS' value-adding quality IT support is being recognized and validation of our technical capabilities." The WMA BPA Professional IT Services includes Software Development, System Administration, DevOps, System and Application Architecture and design, Database management, Data Science, Enterprise Architecture and PaaS/IaaS. This BPA directly supports the Water Mission Area (WMA) and USGS Enterprise Technology Office (ETO) and is responsible for deployment of high-end information technology products to enhance data storage and access methods against natural resource datasets. BPA tasks support the development and enhancement of enterprise software development and data management in collaboration with USGS scientists and other partners. Our support will provide researchers, policy makers, and the general public access to environmental monitoring data and analytic products through web-based interactive geospatial displays and other decision support tools throughout the USGS agency.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_e357c64f59a540c58b7a8dda5a8bbd84~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_740,h_495,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS is awarded Web Redesign contract for the Federal Housing Finance Agency (June 2022) ]]></title><description><![CDATA[NIS is awarded Web Redesign contract for the Federal Housing Finance Agency (June 2022) Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-is-awarded-web-redesign-contract-for-the-federal-housing-finance-agency-june-2022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62d1b661fffde4306c70da12</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 18:50:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_9277aca9063e4763bbc30ba4574708b8~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_600,h_300,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NIS is awarded Web Redesign contract for the Federal Housing Finance Agency (June 2022) Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce a new contract from the Federal Housing Finance Agency (FHFA).   Under this contract, NIS will support FHFA with redesign and development of their on-prem SharePoint website to industry best practice content management system using Drupal Open-Source technology.   The FHFA was created by the Housing and Economic Recovery Act of 2008 (HERA) to regulate and supervise Fannie Mae, Freddie Mac, and the 11 Federal Home Loan Banks (jointly, the "regulated entities").  These institutions play critical roles in supporting our nation's housing finance system.   In the coming year, NIS will re-architect/re-engineer FHFA's SharePoint based public website, <a href="www.FHFA.gov " target="_blank" ><u>www.FHFA.gov </u></a>and migrate to a new FedRAMP certified cloud environment.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_9277aca9063e4763bbc30ba4574708b8~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_600,h_300,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS is awarded a spot on the JAIC DRAID BOA (March 2022)]]></title><description><![CDATA[NIS is proud to announce that it is one of the awardees on the Joint Artificial Intelligence Center (JAIC) Data Readiness for Artificial...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-is-awarded-a-spot-on-the-jaic-draid-boa-march-2022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">624220731fc30db72f3ba54b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 21:08:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_e918db8c1af64f43ab6e4c97b07aacd1~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NIS is proud to announce that it is one of the awardees on the Joint Artificial Intelligence Center (JAIC) Data Readiness for Artificial Intelligence Development (DRAID) Basic Ordering Agreement (BOA). This is a 5-year BOA award with a $241M ceiling.  NIS will provide AI-based IT services to DoD and other federal agencies around data science, data engineering, data architecture, data quality, cloud integration and alignment, software development, and data anonymization.  CK Park, NIS' President & CEO stated "We are excited about the JAIC BOA as this validates our capabilities and experiences.  We are continuing to make technological progress to ensure our capabilities are aligned with next generation technologies like AI, Chatbots, VR, AR, ML and RPA but more importantly assist our customers in leveraging emerging technologies."  For more information on how NIS can assist you, please contact <a href="BD@nw-its.com" target="_blank" >,<u>BD@nw-its.com</u></a> or call 703-750-0453.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_e918db8c1af64f43ab6e4c97b07aacd1~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS is awarded GSA 8(a) STARS III (February 2022)]]></title><description><![CDATA[NIS is proud to announce that we've been awarded a contract on the General Services Administration (GSA) Streamlined Technology...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-is-awarded-gsa-8-a-stars-iii-february-2022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62055dbc5f6f9d86fba723d7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 15:42:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_50a86cc3a48e49578856a8aeab2b6a4a~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_900,h_400,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NIS is proud to announce that we've been awarded a contract on the General Services Administration (GSA) Streamlined Technology Acquisition Resource for Services (STARS) III Governmentwide Acquisition Contract (GWAC).</p>

<p>This best-in-class indefinite delivery indefinite quantity (IDIQ) contract has a $50 billion ceiling that supports the development of 8(a) firms and provides federal agencies a way to deliver mission-critical IT services. 8(a) STARS III represents GSA's efforts to support small businesses while meeting ever-evolving agency requirements. This contract focuses on meeting agency needs for emerging technologies such as artificial intelligence, blockchain, robotic process automation and more. NIS is excited about the opportunity to continue our partnership with GSA to support our federal customers with modernizing their infrastructure, migration to the cloud and supporting emerging technologies. Examples of work to be performed relative to Order requirements include the following: 
 * Data Management 
 * Information and Communications Technology 
 * IT Operations and Maintenance 
 * IT Security / IT workforce augmentation 
 * Software Development 
 * Systems Design</p>

<p>Please visit <a href="http://www.gsa.gov/stars3" target="_blank" >www.gsa.gov/stars3</a> for the most current information on 8(a) STARS III. For more information about how we can support you, email <a href="mailto:stars3@nw-its.com" target="_blank" >stars3@nw-its.com</a> or call 703-750-0453.</p>

<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_50a86cc3a48e49578856a8aeab2b6a4a~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_900,h_400,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Senator Mark Warner recognizes NIS for receiving the HIREVets Platinum Award (February 2022)]]></title><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/sen-mark-warner-recognizes-nis-for-receiving-the-hirevets-palatinum-award-february-2022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">620298c07ebf040624c95749</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 16:22:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_4640ab425001401ca96ec3564bdea905~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_800,h_538,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_fe7965014f224900bf774fd27a6eec24~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS wins NIWC ITSM &#38; Telephony support contract (December 2021)]]></title><description><![CDATA[On December 7, the Naval Information Warfare Center (NIWC) Atlantic awarded Nationwide IT Services (NIS) a contract that provides...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-wins-niwc-itsm-telephony-support-contract-december-2021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61b3cdd69a177e00168b6632</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 22:54:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_09e664c6e55e4450ad014c8be2e86c96~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_740,h_495,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p> On December 7, the Naval Information Warfare Center (NIWC) Atlantic awarded Nationwide IT Services (NIS) a contract that provides technical support for the Integrated Service Center (ISC) Information Technology Service Management (ITSM) and telephony. NIS will provide technical support for Avaya telephony hardware, software, infrastructure, Call Management System (CMS) applications, and Customer Relationship Management (CRM) application support (e.g. BMC Remedy ITSM and Oracle Database, Business Objects/Analytics). CK Park, NIS' President & CEO says, "NIS is excited to continue to our support NIWC and our warfighters. I sincerely appreciate all the outstanding professionals of Team NIS. We are honored and excited to continue our first-class support to NIWC over the next five years."</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_09e664c6e55e4450ad014c8be2e86c96~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_740,h_495,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS wins NIWC Integrated Service Center (ISC) contract (November 2021) ]]></title><description><![CDATA[NIS wins NIWC Integrated Service Center (ISC) contract (November 2021) On November 30, the Naval Information Warfare Center (NIWC)...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-wins-niwc-integrated-service-center-isc-contract-november-2021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61b3ccc6affc100016a4abaf</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 22:53:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_09e664c6e55e4450ad014c8be2e86c96~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_740,h_495,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NIS wins NIWC Integrated Service Center (ISC) contract (November 2021) On November 30, the Naval Information Warfare Center (NIWC) Atlantic awarded Nationwide IT Services (NIS) the Integrated Service Center (ISC) contract supporting over 1 million Navy personnel at 2,500 activities world-wide. NIS will provide 24x7x365 Tier 1-3 functional support for current and future Navy programs supported by ISC and the Information Security (INFOSEC) Technical Assistance Center (ITAC). CK Park, NIS' President & CEO says, "NIS is honored and excited about the opportunity to partner with NIWC to support our warfighters. This is a result of the outstanding work of our team to earn the trust and confidence of our customers at NIWC. We look forward to continuing our first-class support to NIWC over the next five years."</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_09e664c6e55e4450ad014c8be2e86c96~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_740,h_495,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS Receives 2021 HIRE Vets Medallion Award from the U.S. Department of Labor (November 2021)]]></title><description><![CDATA[NOVEMBER 11, 2021 – U.S. Secretary of Labor Martin J. Walsh recognized Nationwide IT Services, Inc. as one of the 849 recipients of the...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-receives-2021-hire-vets-medallion-award-from-the-u-s-department-of-labor-november-2021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">618c48da821f27001717dcb2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 22:35:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_4640ab425001401ca96ec3564bdea905~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_800,h_538,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>NOVEMBER 11, 2021</strong> – U.S. Secretary of Labor Martin J. Walsh recognized Nationwide IT Services, Inc. as one of the 849 recipients of the 2021 HIRE Vets Medallion Award during a virtual award ceremony presented by U.S. Department of Labor. NIS earned the platinum award after applying earlier this year. The Honoring Investments in Recruiting and Employing American Military Veterans Act (HIRE Vets Act) Medallion Program is the only federal award program that recognizes employers who successfully recruit, hire, and retain veterans. </p>
<p>“NIS is honored to be recognized on our efforts on hiring veterans and supporting veterans transition to civilian career,” said President & CEO C.K. Park, who is also an Army veteran. “NIS is grateful to our veterans for their service and sacrifices to our nation while bringing discipline and leadership to our workforce and contributing to our successes at all levels. I am grateful to US Department of Labor for recognizing NIS for our efforts.”</p>
<p>NIS joins 848 other companies from 49 states, plus the District of Columbia, who have shown a commitment to hiring veterans, but also ensuring that they have a long-term career and growth plan that uses the diverse skills they acquired through their military service. </p>
<p>Recipients of the 2021 HIRE Vets Medallion Award meet rigorous employment and veteran integration assistance criteria, including veteran hiring and retention percentages; availability of veteran-specific resources; leadership programming for veterans; dedicated human resource efforts; pay compensation and tuition assistance programs for veterans. More than 1,400 employers have earned a HIRE Vets Medallion Award since 2018.</p>
<p><strong>About Nationwide IT Services</strong></p>
<p>Nationwide IT Services, Inc (NIS) is an IT and Management consulting company, designated 8(a) by the SBA, and a CVE-verified Service Disabled Veteran Owned Small Business. Our mission is to deliver value-added services to our customers, leveraging technology, people, and industry best practices to implement innovative solutions through our trusted employees and team members. </p>
<p><strong>About the HIRE Vets Medallion Program</strong></p>
<p>The HIRE Vets Medallion Award is earned by businesses that demonstrate unparalleled commitment to attracting, hiring, and retaining veterans. The 2022 HIRE Vets Medallion Award application period will open to employers on Jan. 31, 2022. For more information about the program and the application process, visit <a href="https://www.hirevets.gov/" target="_blank" >HIREVets.gov</a>. </p>
<p>There are different awards for large employers (500-plus employees), medium employers (51-499 employees), and small employers (50 or fewer employees). Additionally, there are two award tiers: platinum and gold.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b95a20_4640ab425001401ca96ec3564bdea905~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_800,h_538,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS Wins Recompete of USGS Contract (July 2021)]]></title><description><![CDATA[On July 22, the U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) announced that NIS was awarded the Science Collaboration and Application Services III...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-wins-recompete-of-usgs-contract-july-2021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6134c7ba0ecbbc0016057df4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 13:38:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_e85615ae95f9477eaddd929abfae0bd9~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On July 22, the U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) announced that NIS was awarded the Science Collaboration and Application Services III (SCAS-III) contract to support the Assistant Chief Information Officer (ACIO) for the USGS enterprise. The scope of work includes custom applications development to  telecommunication support, Web Development, enterprise  hosting/collaboration, and network/server administration and increase use of cloud-based environments for both Microsoft Azure and Amazon Web Services (AWS). The new contract, the company’s largest, will last five years and continue to employ people at locations across the country. “NIS is honored and grateful for the trust and confidence of the USGS and appreciate the opportunity to continue our support to ACIO and the agency. Our continued growth is dependent  on providing value-added services with integrity, ethics, and  professionalism.<em>” </em>said NIS President & CEO C.K. Park. NIS looks forward to continuing our partnership with ACIO supporting the important Scientific Mission across the country.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_e85615ae95f9477eaddd929abfae0bd9~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS to Continue Support for the FAA AVS (June 2021)]]></title><description><![CDATA[NIS is pleased to announce that NIS has been awarded a contract to continue our support of the technical and strategic communications...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-to-continue-support-for-the-faa-avs-june-2021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6134c75a126b80001679247d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 13:35:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_974ef072d28047aa99f4bce621d0a8b7~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NIS is pleased to announce that NIS has been awarded a contract to continue our support of the technical and strategic communications support to the FAA, Associate Administrator for Aviation Safety (AVS). The scope of the work includes supporting the strategic communication, Intranet, SharePoint, and  program analysis. NIS has been supporting AVS for over 10 years and this is only possible due to our outstanding team of professionals supporting the AVS leadership. NIS is grateful and excited about  the opportunity to continue to support the important mission of the Aviation Safety.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_974ef072d28047aa99f4bce621d0a8b7~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS is certified as a V3 company (June 2021)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce its certification as a Virginia Values Veterans (V3) company. This certification is...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-certified-as-a-v3-company-june-2021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">60fa9c6fe9403300159f78a8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 10:39:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_6fbdcfca10ed48d0a02326df10def845~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce its certification as a Virginia Values Veterans (V3) company. This certification is part of NIS' commitment to hiring, developing, and retaining Veterans. The Virginia Values Veterans (V3) program trains and certifies employers to help them implement nationally recognized best practices in recruiting, hiring, and retaining highly skilled and dependable Veterans.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_6fbdcfca10ed48d0a02326df10def845~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS awarded DOE Access Control Contract (April 2021)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce that we've been awarded a security contract to support the Department of Energy (DOE)....]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-awarded-doe-access-control-contract-april-2021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">60fa9c6fe9403300159f78a7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 10:39:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_2d588d80ed9c461b9c847f96815190de~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce that we've been awarded a security contract to support the Department of Energy (DOE).  As an important part of the DOE's physical security system, NIS will be providing access control, surveillance, and security testing support for the DOE's Access Control System. This contract includes the operation and maintenance (O&M) of the Access Control System that integrates the physical security, badge readers, closed-circuit television, and associated software for multiple DOE facilities. We are excited about the opportunity to partner with DOE and support its mission to protect the safety of its people and safeguard assets. This is a three (3) year contract.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_2d588d80ed9c461b9c847f96815190de~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS awarded IRS WCMS Contract (October 2020)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce that we’ve been awarded a contract to support the Internal Revenue Service (IRS)....]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-awarded-irs-wcms-contract-october-2020</link><guid isPermaLink="false">60fa9c6fe9403300159f78a6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 10:39:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_0637d5b1fe6d4664adfdc0e3164a5e8a~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nationwide IT Services (NIS) is pleased to announce that we’ve been awarded a contract to support the Internal Revenue Service (IRS).</p>

<p>This contract includes the operations, maintenance, and modernization of the Web Content Management System (WCMS) and Tax Withholding Estimator (TWE) applications both part of <a href="IRS.gov." target="_blank" ><u>IRS.gov.</u></a> </p>

<p>This contract is a result of NIS’ advanced Drupal practice and expertise supporting our customers with web site/application development, hosting, and agile SCRUM, Kanban and Rapid delivery methodologies developed over the years supporting multiple federal agencies.</p>

<p>We are excited about the opportunity to partner with the IRS and support its mission critical websites and applications and add value to the IRS and the taxpayers.</p>

<p>This is a five (5) year contract awarded through the VETS2 GWAC, where NIS is a prime. </p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_0637d5b1fe6d4664adfdc0e3164a5e8a~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS awarded NIWC Atlantic ISC Contract (June 2020)]]></title><description><![CDATA[NIS is pleased to announce that we’ve been awarded a contract supporting the Naval Information Warfare Center (NIWC) Atlantic Integrated...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-awarded-niwc-atlantic-isc-contract-june-2020</link><guid isPermaLink="false">60fa9c6fe9403300159f78a5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 10:39:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_8c9a64d4929242a19cd75cb0be6e60ad~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NIS is pleased to announce that we’ve been awarded a contract supporting the Naval Information Warfare Center (NIWC) Atlantic Integrated Service Center (ISC). This contract will support over 1 million warfighter personnel in 2,500 activities world-wide. NIS will provide tiered level Service Desk support and associated information technology services and integrated enterprise solutions. CK Park, NIS President & CEO says “NIS is excited about the opportunity to continue support of our warfighters. Our continued growth is a result of the great work that our employees and partners do and we look forward to continued success with NIWC.”</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_8c9a64d4929242a19cd75cb0be6e60ad~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIS is awarded OASIS Small Business Pool 1 (March 2020)]]></title><description><![CDATA[NIS is pleased to announce that we have been awarded the General Service Administration (GSA) One Acquisition Solution for Integrated...]]></description><link>https://www.nw-its.com/post/nis-is-awarded-oasis-small-business-pool-1-march-2020</link><guid isPermaLink="false">60fa9c6fe9403300159f78a4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 10:39:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_100438d7591b48dca2e0c724c49d5453~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Brandon Esterle</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NIS is pleased to announce that we have been awarded the General Service Administration (GSA) One Acquisition Solution for Integrated Services (OASIS) Small Business Pool 1 contract.  OASIS provides flexible and innovative solutions for complex professional services with core disciplines in program management services; management consulting services; logistics services; engineering services; scientific services; and financial services.   For more information, contact <u>oasissb@nw-is.com</u> or 703-750-0453.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d518c7_100438d7591b48dca2e0c724c49d5453~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_745,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>